=Love Start From Marriage= =Episode 7=
= الحب يبدأ من الزواج = = الحلقة 7 =
Qianxun.
Qianxun.
It's been a while since we married.
لقد مرت فترة منذ أن تزوجنا.
Maybe we should...
ربما يجب علينا ...
No.
رقم.
Not yet?
ليس بعد؟
What's the reason this time?
ما السبب هذه المرة؟
I...
أنا...
I have
أملك
phobia or disorder in that aspect.
رهاب أو اضطراب في هذا الجانب.
That's fine.
هذا جيّد.
I'll help you cure it.
سوف أساعدك في علاجه.
(No, no. I can't do this.)
(لا ، لا ، لا يمكنني فعل ذلك).
I'll take a bath.
سوف آخذ حماما.
It takes a while. You sleep first.
يستغرق بعض الوقت.  أنت تنام أولاً.
Think I can't deal with you?
أعتقد أنني لا أستطيع التعامل معك؟
Sleep tight, babe.
نوم عميق يا حبيبي.
You're still waiting. Drink some water.
أنت ما زلت تنتظر.  اشرب بعض الماء.
I'm not thirsty.
انا لست عطشان.
You can drink as you like.
يمكنك أن تشرب كما تريد.
Then we can get to the real business.
ثم يمكننا الوصول إلى العمل الحقيقي.
Drink a little.
اشرب قليلا.
Don't waste my effort.
لا تضيع جهدي.
You're not drinking?
أنت لا تشرب؟
(Three.)
(ثلاثة.)
(Two.)
(اثنين.)
(One.)
(واحد.)
(Oh.)
(أوه.)
(Damn it. I must have lost my virginity last night.)
(اللعنة. لابد أنني فقدت عذريتي الليلة الماضية.)
You're up.
أنت جاهز.
Last night, did you...
الليلة الماضية ، هل ...
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't take advantage of the weak.
لن أستغل الضعيف.
I'll wait for your permission.
سأنتظر إذنك.
Besides,
بجانب،
you grind your teeth and snore.
أنت تطحن أسنانك وتشخر.
Who can put up with that?
من يستطيع تحمل ذلك؟
Breakfast is on the table.
الإفطار على الطاولة.
Off to work I go.
خارج للعمل أذهب.
Right. That's her.
الصحيح.  تلك هي.
Stop her!
قف هنا!
That's the woman.
هذه هي المرأة.
-It's the woman that bullies our Sula. -Beat her.
- إنها المرأة التي تتنمر على سولا.  -ضربها.
She seduced Sula's boyfriend.
لقد أغرت صديق سولا.
Beat her.
اضربها.
Have some self-awareness.
لديك بعض الوعي الذاتي.
Wanna be a bitch?
هل تريد أن تكون عاهرة؟
Get divorced and quit.
احصل على الطلاق والاستسلام.
Look how ugly you are.
انظر كم أنت قبيح.
This is what a bully looks like?
هذا ما يبدو عليه المتنمر؟
You shameless bitch.
أنت عاهرة وقحة.
Get the hell out!
أخرجوا من الجحيم!
Can't you be self-aware?
ألا يمكنك أن تكون مدركًا لذاتك؟
-Get divorced and quit. -You shameless mistress.
-اطلق و اترك.  -أنت عشيقة وقحة.
Go to hell!
اذهب إلى الجحيم!